var myObject= {
"grade1":[
{"question":'14+20',"answer":'34'},
{"question":'1-18',"answer":'-17'},
{"question":'15*18',"answer":'270'},
{"question":'14+16',"answer":'30'},
{"question":'12-20',"answer":'-8'},
{"question":'19*11',"answer":'209'},
{"question":'15+14',"answer":'29'},
{"question":'1-3',"answer":'-2'},
{"question":'18*20',"answer":'360'},
{"question":'5+11',"answer":'16'},
{"question":'19-16',"answer":'3'}
],
"grade2":[
{"question":'3+14',"answer":'17'},
{"question":'20-8',"answer":'12'},
{"question":'19*14',"answer":'266'},
{"question":'18+20',"answer":'38'},
{"question":'18-16',"answer":'2'},
{"question":'10*3',"answer":'30'},
{"question":'11+4',"answer":'15'},
{"question":'3-16',"answer":'-13'},
{"question":'1*17',"answer":'17'},
{"question":'15+9',"answer":'24'},
{"question":'2-10',"answer":'-8'}
]
};